there's this other sign and i'm not
bragging just happens to be where i was
i was in sheridan wyoming
thank you
i'll share this with you i was driving
my minivan
because i know you're looking at me
going uh rodney amanda versing caliber
drives me man
please i keep on in the fleet
because i got to do uh some keep bait
the ladies uh back up off me
trust me i know what i'm dealing with
ever since i got up here you've been
staring at me thinking yourself wow
this looks like the loser cousin of jeff
bridges
some of the older people staring at me
thinking he looks just like kenny rogers
at the time he decided to get plastic
surgery
he looks like santa claus gave up
sorry they're getting uh i get the look
of petroleum from a ride they got a
little store there and inside store
beverages and snacks i'm big fan of the
beverages
and the snacks
so i started heading to store okay and
uh is it wine it's a long big parking
lot wyoming they got a lot of space they
got everybody's driving you know
uh tractors and
everybody's got trailers so they'll come
into town for provisions
it's always space so there's a distance
from the from the
liquid petroleum pumps to the to the
store right so i'm walking among the
store here's what happened this dude is
coming out store same time right he's
got a couple things in his arms
and he looks over at me
as he stand there
and he just stops holding the door with
you know with his butt
which i might add it's perfectly suited
for
if you ever get an argument about
intelligent
intelligent design versus evolution
you throw that one out adam boom you win
check me
you ain't coming up with that by chance
so dude sees me and i see him you know
it's kind of an awkward moment i'm kind
of like
you know really just looking at me so i
had to do that kind of weird
you know you're walking and then you got
to like
kind of act like you're running but
she's not really running
the fact she actually goes slower than
if you just kept vlogging
i sort of let them know it's where the
international sign of if i could run
i would do it now
all right so i'm scurrying
screaming over towards him right
obviously you understand something about
me i'm very secure with you i am as a
man
uh that i can handle uh another man
holding a door for me
first of
man i can give another man a hug
a good hug
not that weird
handshake and tap on the shoulder thing
we do that's just gay
or sometimes you do the two taps in your
out hug
two taps quit touching me hug you know
what i'm saying not me two taps i go in
tighter
if i'm feeling it from the dude i'll
lift him up and pop his back
that's how secure i am
[Applause]
so i get i get it i get i get to the
door right
right yeah and and i go
all right because that's what we do
dudes
hey
so we need everything we need to say
right
hey thanks you're welcome uh if you have
time or go you don't come fishing with
me well i really like it we're just
passing through yeah well i got a nice
boat hey that's pretty cool is that was
it your boat over there yeah that was my
boat
that was pretty cool
all that was
all right
because if it's two ladies it gets weird
you know what i mean
it's gotta turn it into a thing right
here right because one of these like
hey i just uh wanted you to know
that i really appreciate that you took
your time uh to wait for me and stand
here and hold the door because you
didn't have to hold the door because i
was so far away that you could have just
kept going and you didn't have to stop
but obviously you got things going on in
your life and you got a lot of harms are
full of stuff and your family's waiting
for you and you just took a moment to
hold the door for me and i just want you
to know that even though it wasn't it's
not a big thing it is a big thing to me
because it's the little things that
really matter and i just want you to
know that i totally and truly appreciate
what you've done
well i want you to know that i truly
appreciate that you took our time to
appreciate what i was doing because i'm
not trying to make any big statements
i'm not trying to break down the
patriarchy or anything i'm just trying
to be a nice person and people just need
to be nice to people don't people's just
so mad about everything and all the time
and i just think just little time
pleasantries just being nice to each
other it's what we really need to do
[Music]
that is so true i just completely
understand exactly what you're saying i
think that we need to show the world
that people are still nice people this
world would you let me take a picture of
you can we take a picture let's get a
picture just say that
that is perfect i'm going to post it i'm
going to put it on my instagram it's
just
now what's your name
okay
oh my goodness you know denise from
denver you know denise from denver
well of course i know denise who did
ever we've been friends forever we just
did a little la route together and then
we got lots of stuff and people weren't
buying the lularoo because it's like
once you have you know 10 or some pieces
of little room you pretty much have
everything you're ever going to need
from the room
so now we decided you know what we
should do we should do the candles and
so we started doing
we just started doing the new england
candles because they're really nice but
they have to they came out the three
weeks and i just understand why you have
to do the three weeks because they're
always strong enough with one weight and
then you do the three weeks it's just
too strong then you gotta open the
window and then what's the point of
adding a candle you're just gonna open
the window and then but if you only
light one of the wicks it burns down off
of that one side and then you get scatty
wampus and it kind of ruins the
aesthetic of the candle to begin with it
just kind of defeats the purpose if you
have just three weeks
that's what i didn't tell the people i
don't understand their favorites now
they're giving me almost five weeks
that's just crazy so i started doing
scentsy candles
sassy candles that's what we've been
doing i love the city candles because
you can get more of a party which is
[Laughter]
or you know something like that
[Applause]
[Music]
mhm